fantasymovieleague.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy - Fantasy Movie League

_Last Updated: September 29, 2017_

National CineMedia, LLC (" **NCM** ," " **Us** ," or " **We** ") is committed to protecting the privacy of the users of NCM’s online service which consists of, among other things, websites, mobile applications, games, software that you have downloaded or are about to download, any software that you have embedded on a website or are about to embed, any applications created by NCM and available through social networking sites or other websites or on mobile platforms, any software running on NCM’s servers, content, related documentation, information on NCM domains, and information made available by users to each other through the services (these websites and mobile applications and the software and services provided or offered through these web sites and mobile applications, regardless of the platform from which it is accessed, whether existing now or in the future, are collectively referred to as the " **Sites** " and individually referred to as the " **Site** "). This Privacy Policy (the " **Policy** ") discloses NCM’s information privacy practices for each Site and is intended to inform registered users and other visitors to the Sites of the data collection and use practices of the Sites.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, please contact NCM by e-mail at [customerservice@ncm.com](mailto:customerservice@ncm.com).

**Registered Users.**

While Registration is not required to access the public areas of the Sites, it is, required for access to certain areas of the Sites and the products and services provided through those areas of the Sites. The areas of the Sites requiring registration are noted on each Site, and may include additional terms and conditions regarding the collection and use of your information.

When you provide information to NCM to register for an account, your profile information will be retained by NCM. When you identify yourself on a Site, you may identify yourself through a social network account in which NCM may receive additional personal information about you. In each case, NCM will collect and record the information you provide.

Users registering for an account on one of the Sites may receive a username and password to access their account and portions of the Site available to registered users. A username and password on one of the Sites may not be valid on all Sites and separate accounts for each Site may be required. When accessing the portions of that Site available to account holders, users may be required to provide their username and password.

You are solely responsible for your account and all uses of your username and password. IN ORDER TO PROTECT YOUR PRIVACY, DO NOT SHARE YOUR USERNAME OR PASSWORD WITH OTHERS.

**Personally Identifiable Information.**

Personally identifiable information ("PII") is information by which you may be personally identified, either directly or in combination with other information. We only collect and share personally identifiable information regarding users of the Sites as described in this Policy. Except as noted in this Policy, PII collected on the Sites is NOT sold, rented, or shared with third parties without your consent. What constitutes PII is subject to change under applicable law.

We may automatically collect PII from you when you access the Sites. We may also collect PII from you when you provide information to us on or through a number of the Sites, such as responses, registrations, reviews, comments, emails, postings, photographs, messages, the interfacing with social networking sites or other electronic submissions and communications sent by you to NCM or the Sites. The PII we collect from you may include:   

  * Domain name and IP address;
  * E-mail address;
  * Contact information (including, name, address, zip code, country, and phone number);
  * Age;
  * Gender;
  * Marital status;
  * Occupation and position;
  * Employer;
  * Income information;
  * Financial information, such as account or credit card numbers;
  * Mobile phone number, mobile carrier's name, unique identifier for a mobile device and the date, time and content of mobile communications with NCM;
  * GPS, Bluetooth or other location-based or geo-positioning information, including your presence within participating theatres and retail locations;
  * Audit Information;
  * User-specific and aggregate information on areas of the Sites accessed;
  * Username and password information for each Site; and
  * Other information volunteered by you, such as information provided through responses, registrations, reviews, comments, emails, postings, photographs, messages, the interfacing with social networking sites (such as a profile photo, birthday and status), or other electronic submissions and communications sent by you to NCM or the Sites.

BY USING THE SITES, YOU CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PII. YOU SHOULD NOT PROVIDE NCM WITH ANY PII (OR SUBMIT OR POST ANY PII TO ANY OF THE SITES) UNLESS YOU WOULD LIKE THAT INFORMATION TO BE USED BY NCM IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS POLICY. LIKEWISE, YOU SHOULD NOT SUBMIT OR POST ANY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION TO ANY OF THE SITES UNLESS YOU WANT THAT INFORMATION TO BE ACCESSIBLE BY OTHER USERS OF THE SITE, AS INFORMATION POSTED ON A SITE MAY BE MADE AVAILABLE TO OTHER USERS OF THAT SITE.

PII that NCM collects from users of the Sites (both registered and unregistered) may be used for a variety of purposes, for example to provide the services and products offered through the Site, to fulfill prizes for NCM’s games, to customize advertising and other content displayed on the Site and/or the layout of the Site for each individual user of the Site, to notify users of the Site about updates to and activities on the Site and about goods and services that we feel may be of interest to you, to improve the content of the Sites, to analyze data and patterns regarding usage of the Site, to contact users of the Site for marketing purposes, and to contact users of the Site for information verification purposes.

We may also share certain PII with third party companies so that they may offer products and services to users of our Sites that we believe will be of interest to those users. We may also share certain PII with third party ad serving companies to better target the advertising and other content displayed on the Sites and provide pertinent offers we think may be of interest to our users. In addition, third party advertisers may receive certain PII about you if you click on advertisements displayed on the Sites (and clicking on any advertisement displayed on the Sites will be considered your consent to "opt in" for this data collection).

The Sites have features that allow you to store and share your information or content with others. The Sites may include features and functions that allow you to post and share content, messages and reviews to forums, message boards, chat rooms or bulletin boards or to interact with other users through fantasy features or other games that we may from time to time make available. We may record and store archives of these communications and content on our servers. You acknowledge and consent to the recording and storage of such communications and content. If you choose to provide PII through use of these features, that information may be available to a wider community and individuals reading this information may use it or disclose it to other individuals or entities not under our control and without your knowledge. We recommend that you think carefully about sharing this type of information, including through forums, message boards, chat rooms or bulletin boards. Any action you perform or information about yourself that you share with others (including other game players) is considered public, and at your own discretion.

**Mobile Applications.**

If you use our mobile applications on a mobile device and your settings allow it, we may collect information about your location within participating theatres and retail locations through your mobile device's Bluetooth, Wi-Fi or similar capabilities based on the detection of signals from nearby proximity beacons and Wi-Fi networks. We will only gather these kinds of location information if you agree to share them with us by opting-in within the mobile application(s) (either during your initial login or later) and by enabling these capabilities on your mobile device. Once you have opted-in to receive offers and information and consented to our use of location information, the mobile application will continue to collect location information (even if it is running in the background) until you opt-out, log-off or use your phone's or other device's setting to disable your mobile device's applicable geolocation, GPS, Bluetooth or similar capabilities for the application. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" section below for more information on how to limit the location information that we may collect from your mobile device.

**Personal Profiles.**

We may also provide you with the ability to create a personal profile or avatar on a Site containing PII provided by you and to make your personal profile or avatar available to other users of the Sites. You may adjust the scope and nature of the information you make available to other users of the Sites through Your personal profile as indicated on the Sites. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR THE INFORMATION INCLUDED IN YOUR PERSONAL PROFILE AND SHARED WITH OTHER USERS OF THE SITES. YOU SHOULD NOT CREATE A PERSONAL PROFILE UNLESS YOU WANT TO SHARE YOUR PII WITH OTHER USERS OF THE SITES.

**Disclosure as Required by Law.**

Though we make every reasonable effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose PII of certain users of a Site when we have a reasonable and good-faith belief that the disclosure is necessary to enforce the Terms of Use for the Sites, comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or other legal process, or to otherwise enforce or protect NCM's rights under applicable law, including, without limitation, NCM's intellectual property rights. In this situation we will use reasonable efforts to provide notice of this disclosure to all affected users, to the extent reasonably possible under the circumstances.

**Enhancement of Personal Information.**

We may combine and enhance our user database information and Activity Information (as defined below) with third party data and information to better target our advertising and provide pertinent offers in which we think our users would be interested. Certain summary demographics are also used in our research for product offerings. Individual PII is never used in our research product offering and is never tied back to an individual user or resold for any purposes.

**Service Announcements.**

On occasion it is necessary to send out service related announcements. For instance, if our Sites or any of the services offered through the Sites are temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their accounts. These communications are not promotional in nature.

**Special Offers and Updates.**

We may send new registrants of the Sites a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members may occasionally also receive information on products, services and special deals, and periodic newsletters. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" section below.

**Choice and Opt-out.**

We provide you with a choice whether to receive certain emails. We provide you the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having your PII used for certain purposes. If you are a user of the Sites and you no longer wish to receive, email, mail, or telephone calls from us or have your email address or postal address shared with third parties, you may opt-out of receiving email, mail or telephone calls from us or having your email address or postal address shared with third parties.

If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers' target-audience preferences, you can opt-out by emailing us as set forth below. In addition, if you would prefer that we not share your personally identifiable information with third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes, you may opt-out of having your PII shared with third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes.

All opt-out requests can be made by emailing us at: [unsubscribe@ncm.com](mailto:unsubscribe@ncm.com) or writing us at Attn: Customer Service, 9110 E. Nichols Ave #200, Centennial, CO 80112. Certain communications from us may also contain an unsubscribe link for you to opt-out from receiving future similar communications.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our Sites. These companies may use PII or non-PII (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to the Sites and other web sites or applications in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative, a coalition of online advertising networks that provides an opportunity for consumers to opt-out of targeted advertising by member companies. It should be noted that opting out does not mean you will not see advertisements online, but these advertisements will not be targeted based on your online user interest profile.

If you access any of our Sites through a mobile device, you may adjust the settings on your mobile device to allow or prevent the sharing of location information. For example, you can disable "Location" (or "Location Services" on iOS-based devices) on your mobile device to prevent sharing your location information with NCM, or only disable "Bluetooth" to prevent the sharing of information collected via nearby Bluetooth proximity beacons. Please note that if you disable the sharing of location information, you may be unable to access some features of our Sites that are designed for mobile devices.

**Children.**

The Sites are not directed to children under 13 years of age and the Terms of Use for the Sites specifically prohibits use of the Sites by children under 13 years of age. Children under 13 may not use or access the Sites under any circumstances. If you are 13 or older and younger than 18 (or the age of majority in the state in which you reside), then you may access and use the Site only if you have your parents' or guardians' prior permission. NCM does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. If you believe we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13, please let us know and we will remove that information as soon as is reasonably possible.

**Customer Service.**

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and with regard to issues relating to their account, we reply via email, in accordance with the users' wishes.

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information and Activity Information.**

Additionally, in order to provide the best possible service and to allow us to make certain internal reports and make recommendations for improving the Sites and your user experience, we collect aggregate information about the use of the Sites (including information about users accessing the Sites or playing NCM’s games), such as IP addresses, browser type, browser language, referring / exit pages and URLs, other browser history, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, and the date and time and also IDFAs, UDIDs, GPS, Bluetooth or other location-based or geo-positioning information, including your presence within participating theatres and retail locations (as more further described above under Mobile Applications) (collectively, " **Activity Information** "). This Activity Information allows us to improve the content of the Sites and facilitate market research. Sometimes, we utilize the services of a third party to help us understand this information better, although the information that is disclosed to these entities remains at all times in anonymous and non-personally identifiable form. Other than improving the Sites and the experience of visitors to the Sites, we make no other use of this information. The treatment of non-PII is subject to change in accordance with the then applicable law.

**Cookies, Pixels and Web Beacons.**

"Cookies" are commonly used pieces of information in the form of small files that are placed on an individual's computer hard drive to enable the individual to more easily communicate and interact with the Sites. We may use cookies for various purposes, for example to save user preferences, customize content of the Sites for individual users, to ensure that users are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, to record session information, such as items that users add to their shopping cart, to alert users to new areas that might be of interest upon return to the Sites, and to save certain information about users of the Sites and others who visit the Sites, in order to facilitate and enhance interaction with the Sites. NCM does not use cookies to retrieve information from a computer that is unrelated to NCM or the Sites.

A cookie does not collect or keep your name or other PII; however, we may link the information obtained through cookies to other PII to give us a better understanding of your preferences, so that we can provide a more meaningful experience to you on our Sites.

We may use an outside ad serving company to display advertisements on the Sites. The ad serving company may place and collect cookies when it displays an ad on the Sites. We do not have access to information that would confirm the use of cookies by the ad serving company. We may also use third party providers to analyze data and patterns regarding use of the Sites and such third party providers may use cookies, web beacons, tracking pixels, tracking agents or any other visitor identification technology to collect such information.

Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions.

**Access, Review, Update.**

Should you wish to review, delete or update the personal information you provided to us through a Site or that NCM retains about you, please email us at [customerservice@ncm.com](mailto:customerservice@ncm.com).

**Other Web Sites; Links; Widgets.**

Certain of the websites of NCM’s affiliates, promotional partners, advertisers, sponsors, and other third-party websites and third-party widgets are accessible through the Sites. These third party websites and third-party widgets have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. NCM IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY ACTIONS OR PRIVACY POLICIES OF SUCH THIRD PARTIES. YOU SHOULD CHECK THE APPLICABLE PRIVACY POLICIES OF THOSE THIRD PARTIES WHEN PROVIDING PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION THROUGH LINKED WEB SITES AND WIDGETS.

**Consent to the Use of Third Party Providers.**

In addition to the third parties noted in this Policy, NCM may also contract with other third parties to provide various services to NCM relating to the Sites on an outsourced basis rather than performing the services itself. For example, NCM may contract with an email provider to handle the distribution of email messages to users of the Sites. Likewise, NCM may contract with a website hosting provider to host all or a portion of the Sites for NCM. NCM may also contract with third party mobile providers to enable the mobile user services provided through the Sites. We may also use a third party provider to serve ads and collect and analyze data and patterns regarding usage of the Sites. We require these third parties to keep personal information confidential, use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them, and to treat such information in accordance with this Policy. By visiting the Sites, all visitors consent to NCM providing both PII and non-PII received from Site users to these third party providers for the purpose of enabling the third party providers to provide these outsourced services to NCM.

In addition, all Site users consent to the collection, maintenance, and processing of their PII and non-PII by NCM and these third party providers as follows:

_Cookie and Pixel Information_ : Cookies and pixels provide NCM and its providers with the ability to create an ID in order for NCM and its providers to match collected data to an anonymous machine including:  

  * The URLs (or website address) of web pages which have been viewed;
  * The date and time of visit to a web page;
  * Whether the user has clicked on an ad of one of our advertisers, visited their website, or undertaken a transaction with them.

_Session Information_ : This information relates to user, campaign and interest-based history and is used for frequency capping and interest targeting. This information is gathered from websites visited and clicks registered by the user’s machine.

_Request-based Information_ : The following information is passed to NCM and its providers by the user’s computer browser with every request and is stored entirely anonymously for statistical purposes only:  

  * IP (Internet Protocol) addresses - Every device connected to the Internet has an IP address. This cannot be traced to an individual user but can be used for geographic targeting and statistical measurements;
  * Browser type;
  * Computer Operating System.

_Mobile Device Information_ : The following information is passed to NCM and its providers by the mobile communications with NCM:  

  * Mobile phone number;
  * Mobile carrier's name;
  * Unique identifier for a mobile device (e.g. IDFA, UDID or equivalent);
  * Date, time and content of communication with NCM.

**Consent to the Interface with Social Networking Sites.**

In order to enhance your experience on the Sites, NCM may retrieve and collect information about you from your account(s) on various social networking sites, but only if you voluntarily provide it to us, in accordance with the policies and terms of the applicable social networking site. The information you allow us to access varies by social networking site, and it is affected by the privacy settings you establish with the social networking site. By accessing or using the Sites in connection with a social networking site(s), you authorize us to collect, store and use in accordance with this Policy any and all information that you agreed the social network site could provide us. In addition, some social networking sites have features which allow you to send information about your activity on the Sites back to the social networking site (for example, to be published in your profile). If you choose to use these features, then your activity on the Sites will be shared with the social networking site(s). Individuals reading this information on social networking site(s) may use it or disclose it to other individuals or entities without our control and without your knowledge.

NCM may also make certain of its applications available through social networking sites (" **SNS Apps** "). When you use an SNS App on your social network page or use an SNS App on someone else's page, we may record information regarding the use of that SNS App, and we may collect other information that is visible on your social network page in accordance with the relevant terms of use associated with that page. Note that since NCM software may be served through SNS Apps, it is your responsibility to read and accept their Terms of Use, as well as Privacy Policy prior to continuing, as you will be subject to the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy of such SNS Apps. You may also provide us with another person's contact information for purposes of delivering information through SNS Apps. We use this information to contact and, if necessary, remind that person that he or she has been invited to join NCM’s applications or received content through an SNS App. All invitees are provided with the option not to receive further invitations from NCM. We may disclose such information if required to do so in order to comply with legal process, as described above.

**Location Serving.**

As part of the services offered by the Sites, we may display a map via the Bing Maps API or Google Maps API. [Click here](https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/privacystatement) to view Microsoft's Privacy Policy and [click here](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) to view Google’s Privacy Policy. If you allow a mobile Site to get your location, we may collect, depending on the capabilities of your mobile device, information about the Wi-Fi routers closest to you, cell ids of cell towers closest to you and the strength of your Wi-Fi or cell signal. While we use this information to return an estimated location, location data may not be accurate. Please see the "Choice and Opt-out" section above for more information on how to limit the location information that we may collect from your mobile device.

**International Users.**

If you are located outside of the United States, please note that the Sites are hosted on computer servers located in the United States. Therefore, your information will be processed and stored in the United States. As a result, United Sates federal and state governments, courts or law enforcement or regulatory agencies may be able to obtain access to your information through applicable United States laws. Your use of a Site or the your submission of any PII to us will constitute your consent to the transfer of your PII outside of your home country, including the United States, which may have very different date protection and privacy rules and regulations than in your home country. If you do not consent to this transfer of your information, you may not use the Sites or the Services.

**Notification of Changes.**

We will modify this Policy if our privacy practices change. We will notify you of such changes by posting the modified version on the Sites, indicating the date it was last modified, and, if the changes are significant, we will seek your consent to the new or different uses of your information. The date this Policy was last modified is at the top of this page. Please periodically review this Policy so that you are familiar with the current Policy and aware of any changes.

**Security.**

We use reasonable physical, technical and organizational measures to protect the information under our control against accidental or unlawful destruction, or accidental loss, alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access. While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information. For example, our policy is that only those individuals who need your PII to perform a specific job are granted access to that PII. Likewise, all employees and contractors are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices and must be in compliance with such practices. Furthermore, when NCM transfers and receives certain types of sensitive information such as financial or health information, it redirects visitors to a secure server. Finally, the servers that we store PII on are kept in a secure environment. While we employ the above steps, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to NCM and you do so at your own risk.

**Contact Information.**

All inquiries concerning this Policy and the Sites in general may be sent to [customerservice@ncm.com](mailto:customerservice@ncm.com).

**Transfer of Information.**

If NCM elects, in its reasonable discretion, to transfer ownership or control of the Sites to a third party, whether or not in the context of an acquisition of NCM or a merger of NCM with a third party, you consent to the transfer of your PII and non-PII by NCM to that third party, provided that all use of your information by that third party remains subject to the terms of this Policy.

**Do Not Track Policy.**

Some browsers have a "do not track" feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want your online activities tracked. At this time, the Sites do not respond to web browser "do not track" requests or similar signals that users may employ. because a uniform technological standard has not yet been developed. We continue to review new technologies and may adopt a standard once one is created.

**Your California Privacy Rights.**

California law provides that California residents have a right to request that businesses tell them how their PII has been shared with third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes. However, there is an exception to this requirement for businesses that have adopted and disclosed, in their privacy policy, a policy of not disclosing a person’s PII to third parties for those third parties’ direct marketing purposes if that person has exercised an option to opt-out of the disclosure of their PII to third parties for such purposes.

NCM has adopted a policy of allowing you to opt-out of the disclosure of your personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes and thus falls within this exception. Instructions for opting out can be found in the section below entitled "Choice and Opt-Out."

**Thank you for visiting the Sites.**
